hallo ladies and gentlemen welcome back to Tech Showdown
女士们，先生们，欢迎回到Tech Showdown
my name is kevin, this is my co-host teddy
我是Kevin，这是我的搭档teddy
and today we'll be covering  ryzen, here i have the ryzen 7 1800x
今天我们将研究ryzen，在这里我有一个ryzen 7 1800x
and we're going to be doing a showdown against the intel i7 6900k Broadwell e cpu
并且我们将与intel i7 6900k Broadwell e cpu做对比
so it's going to be x370 versus x99
所以这将也是x370 vs x99
now i'm not go all over all the features between these two cpus
我并不打算涉及到它们的方方面面
most you guys probably knows them all anyway so there's not really much point out basically
不管怎么说，你们大多数都了解它们，所以这里没必要很细节地指出
just say they are both eight core cpus both 16 threads
它们都是8核16线程的cpu
and on top speed wise  I will set them both to 4 GHz on all of their eight cores
并且在最高的速度下，我会将它们全都设置为4GHz
just to keep it nice and easy and that regard
仅是为保持简约、优秀和那方面的
so talk a little bit now about the overclocking and then we'll go into the benchmarks
现在来谈一下超频，然后我们将进入评分测试
so overclocking the 1800x was a very interesting of fear
关于1800x(ryzen)的超频有趣得有些可怕
I was talking to Steve from Hardware Unboxed and Bryan from Tech City a lot lately
我之前和Hardware的Steve以及Tech City的Bryan谈论许多
and end up because we all been trying to overlock our ryzen cpus
并且因为我们都试图让我们的ryzen cpus超频而结束
and it just seems very very strange so no matter what I did it would not go above 4 Ghz
这看起来非常非常奇怪，无论我做什么都不会超过4GHz
It would just sit there it would not go to 4.1
它只会停在那里，不会达到4.1
you might be saying to me what kevin it says on the box that it goes to 4GHz
你可能会对我说，盒子上说它达到4GHz，Kevin
who has sure but it will only do it on one core the rest set for me at 3.7 GHz
谁知道呢，不过它只在一个核心达到，其余的是3.7 GHz
so it only do it on that one and so x5*
所以只做那个, x5也是
It actually went up a bit higher than that it was actually closer to 4.1 on that sigle core
所以它实际上比其他核更接近4.1
but hmm yeah I thought that was kind of thing and then when I went to go to some overclocking
我认为这是一种情况，然后当我去一些超频
I thought getting them all eight on 4 GHz would be a cake work
我认为让8核全部达到4 GHz会是个简单的工作
but note was very very difficult
但这其实非常非常困难
I had a lot of trouble
我有很多的麻烦
and yeah it's just a lot of people aren't really managing to get as it right now
现在很多人都无法尽力去实现它
from everything I've heard from all the other reviews and other people in the industry
从一切我在其他评价和业内人士那里听到的
it seems like 4.x or 4 GHz or 4.1
它似乎是4.x或4 GHz或4.1
seems to be the goal you maybe if you get luck you get 4.1 to other of them
似乎是你的目标，如果你运气好，得到4.1之外的
but they do not go much higher than that
但无法更高
and with that being said i have to set the memory to 2133 MHz
并且我必须将内存设置为2133 MHz
Ah I am just to keep it at 4GHz right even touch the memory a little bit
我只能将它保持在4GHz，即使改动一点点内存
it just wasn't having it so very interesting in the overclocking department
它始终无法达到4.1，所以这在超频方面有点意思
however first let's talk about the space of rig
不过首先，让我们来谈一谈配置
so the x370 rig was running the Aorus Gaming 5 motherboard
所以x370(ryzen)运行在Aorus Gaming 5主板上
very very solid data of bus running the exact same
相同的总线数据，运行的十分稳定
Corsair Dominator Platinum memory at 2133MHz
Corsair Dominator Platinum的内存，2133MHz
the same GPU the Gigabyte G1 Gaming GTX1080
相同的GPU显卡 Gigabyte G1 Gaming GTX1080
so it was nice and fair and that regard I tried to match everything is best I could to give you guys
我试图为你们做到我能做到的最好配置，这很公正优秀
the most fair showdown I possible can
我可以做到的最公平的对比
so show you what the Broadwell e this section of my personal rig
接下来给你展示我的intel Broadwell e的配置
this is the specs on it so closely at 6900k same Memory same GPU all the rest of it
和6900k差不多，剩下的内存、显卡配置都一样
most of these guys are running pretty decent multiple just well
这之中的大多数都运行的很好
so it's not like they're running a bad motherboard
不像运行在一个垃圾主板上
the MSI x99A is Gaming Pro Carbon. It is very solid MOBO
这个MSI x99A是游戏特化，这是很稳定的主板。
and the same with that also gaming five order
剩下5个硬件配置也一样
I would think there're still improvements to be made there
我认为这还能再优化
on that Gigabyte board which can be handled later on through BIOS update
技嘉主板在之后还能再更新BIOS
without further do let's jump into the benchmarks and see
无需再费周折，让我们赶快开始评分测试
how the 1800x performs vs 6900k
1800x(ryzen)对比6900k(intel)表现如何
so first we gonna do some productivity stuff and we're going to be jumping into some game benchmarks
首先我们要做一些有生产力的测试，我们要开始一些游戏评分测试
at all three major resolutions 1080p 1440p and 4k so let's get into
主要三种分辨率：1080P 1440P和4K。让我们开始吧
Cinebench R15 测试评分（单线程）
Cinebench R15 测试评分 （多线程）
Handbrake软件转码13分1080p视频所需时间
3dMark 物理测试（火力打击 极限模式1440p）
3dMark 综合测试（火力打击 极限模式1440p）
阴影测试 DX11 1080p
阴影测试 DX11 1440p
阴影测试 DX11 2160p
Dirt Rally(大地长征)游戏帧率测试 DX11 1080p
Dirt Rally(大地长征)游戏帧率测试 DX11 1440p
Dirt Rally(大地长征)游戏帧率测试 DX11 2160p
杀出重围：人类分裂 游戏帧率测试 DX12 1080p
杀出重围：人类分裂 游戏帧率测试 DX12 1440p
杀出重围：人类分裂 游戏帧率测试 DX12 2160p
古墓奇兵崛起 游戏帧率测试 DX12 1080p
古墓奇兵崛起 游戏帧率测试 DX12 1440p
古墓奇兵崛起 游戏帧率测试 DX12 2160p
and we're back so quite interesting there
我们回来了，十分有趣
you see the productivity results are phenomenal with 1800x so very very good
你可以看到1800X(ryzen)的生产力表现是多么的出色
and all of them it beats the 6900k
所有这些都击败了6900K
and that's saying a lot considering the price points coming out
这是考虑到价格的角度来说的
which we'll talk about the little bit later
稍后我们谈一谈
be a very very productivity
非常非常有生产力
however interestingly enough we go to gaming
不过有趣的是当我们去玩游戏
with the exception of day 6 which I think was getting GPU border next *
除了第6天，我认为到达了GPU的瓶颈
and that's why those scores were pretty much the same on both cpus
这就是为什么这些分数在两个cpu上都是差不多的
the 1080p results were quite this warning to me if I'm honestly guys
说实话，这个1080p的结果对我来说是一个警告
I expected better than that
我期望比那更好
however when we wind up through the resolution to go to a lot more solid
但提高分辨率后它的性能就更稳定了
and it's just quite a bizarre thing you think with such great productivity scores
而且，对于有这样生产力的高分，这是一个非常奇怪的事情
and it would also do quite well in the games 1080p and that would scale upwards
在1080p游戏中也做得很好，而且1080p之上也是
but now it's quite bizarre that i'm not really one hundred percent sure
但是奇怪的是现在我不能百分百确定
what's going on it was very confusing to me when I actually was doing the testing
当我正在进行测试时，发生了什么事情对我来说非常混乱
those are the results and i ran every benchmark twice
这些评分，是我完完整整测试两遍的结果
to make sure these were very very accurate so these are all as accurate as i can get them to be
以确保这些数据非常精确，所以这些都是准确的，在我的能力范围内。
be quite interesting there let's move over now and talk about temperatures thing
相当有趣的是，我们现在来谈谈温度事情
so as I said earlier this is running at 4 GHz in order to keep it at that overclocked
就像我刚才所说，运行在4Ghz来超频
if you can even call that
如果你想称那是超频的话
I had to run 1.42 volts
我不得不使用1.42伏的电压
that's quite a bit and I tried 1.41
我还试过1.41
and it was it's not having it so 1.42 was just it has to be there
1.41到不了4Ghz，只有1.42可以，1.42是必要的
but even at that voltage with the deep cool cooler on there that they're cooler 120 mile**
但即使在那个电压下，在风扇冷却的配合下温度也十分的稳定
and it was doing quite well it was hovering and at *x264 stress test after you know 15 minutes
它的表现很好，在悬停在x264压力测试的15分钟里
it would sit sort of high sixties and maybe really touch 70 degrees
它基本都在60多度，有时会接近70度
and that's really really solid
这真的很稳定
AMD it's a big wind here because obviously they sold her down
AMD掀起了一股狂潮，他们几乎卖空了她(ryzen)
they are leads so that's really really good
他们在引领，所以这真的很棒。
Intel just please oh my god this is one thing you could  learn from AMD so please copy
哦，intel这是你可以从AMD身上学到的东西，何不借鉴一下
because the temperatures were actually very very solid
因为温度实际上非常稳定
i do not know what the similimity it is i can tell you for sure
我不知道有什么相似的限制, 但我可以确切的告诉你
there was no some* throwing
温度没有很大的跨度
but if you guys know what a semo* limit is
不过如果你知道什么限制
please let me know in the comments section down below
请在下面的评论区让我知道
because I don't know what it was but it was the most of time in the stress tests
因为我不知道是什么，而这是在压力测试时间中最重要的
it was sitting like 67 68 type thing
它保持在67、68度，这个样子
and when you're playing games that would probably sit around and 63 or something like that
当你玩游戏的时候，大概会在63度这个样子
see a very solid in the temperatures department
在温度方面非常稳定
which brings us now to the conclusion basically and what do I make
这些信息能给我们得出基本的结论，我对
of the Ryzen 7 1800x cpu and how does it compare to Broadwell e
Ryzen 7 的所做，它与Broadwell e的比较
so it does great and productivity if you're a streamer and editor a heavy multitasker
所以如果你从事流媒体编辑或经常开多个高CPU的任务
anyone who needs it for needs a good cpu for productivity type stuff
适合所有需要一个高生产力的cpu的朋友
this is going to be absolutely fantastic
这绝对是梦幻级的
if you have a business and you're considering to buy these type of cpus
如果你做生意，你正在考虑购买这些类型的cpus
like maybe you were stuck on Broadwell E before Haswell E
也许你在Haswell E之前被困在Broadwell E上
you need it for the productivity touch stuff to keep everything nice and efficient
你需要它的高生产力来保持一切的美好高效
definitely take a look at these guys if you're not doing any gaming at all
绝对要看这些(ryzen 7)，如果你们不玩游戏
this is going to be a very very solid cpu in terms of productivity
这将是一个高生产力很稳定的cpu
however when we get to gaming it gets a little bit more weired
但是当我们进行游戏时，它会变得有些奇怪
at 1080p I was quite disappointed I expected more and the 1080p results
在1080p我相当失望，我预计1080p相能有更好的结果
weren't really ideal at 1440p it was starting to look better and at 4k it was pretty solid
在1440p的时候也不是很理想，但它开始看起来更好，在4k是非常可靠的
so yeah in gaming and if you're a person that is only going to be buying a ryzen cpu
所以在游戏方面，如果你是一个只会买一个ryzen cpu的人
not gona to do any productitity at all just straight pure gaming
不要做任何生产力，纯碎是去玩游戏的
then i would say you're probably better off going with Kybe Lake CPU honestly
那么说实话，你最好用Kybe Lake CPU
even like it 7600k would be more solid than this
就像7600k会比这更稳定
if all you are doing is gaming
如果你所做的都是游戏
now it's still a powerful CPU don't get me wrong price-wise when we compare it to 6900k it wins big time
现在它还是一个很好的cpu，在价格方面，当我们与6900k比较时，它大大赢了
so these are the prices in New Zealand
所以这些是新西兰的价格
so the eighteen hundreds coming into the pretty solid price and then look at the 6900k
所以1800x的价格十分的nice，然后看看6900k
wow what a jump so it is a huge price discrepancy there between these 2 eight-core cpus
多么大的差异，在这两个八核CPU之间
and when you bring that into it i would say that I can really recommend the 1800x
当你给我看这些价格时，我会说我真的推荐1800x
if you are a person doing productivity and gaming
如果你是一个做生产的和游戏的人
especially if you're a person like me who runs a 4k display
特别是如果你是像我这样一个使用4k显示器的人
or if you're someone running at 1440p displays it would also be very solid
或者如果你是一个运行在1440p显示器的人，那也将是非常稳固的
if you are a person running a high refresh rate monitor at 1080p
如果你是一个使用1080p高刷新率的显示器的人
say it's 1080p 144Hz and you probably do want to go towards Kaby Lake
比如是1080p 144Hz，你可能要转去Kaby Lake(intel 处理器架构代号)
as i said earlier we definitely want to go towards Kaby Lake
正如我刚才所说，我们绝对更需要Kaby Lake
so yeah that's basically how I'm going to sum up this showdown
所以，这些基本上是我对这次展示的总结
if you're a pure gamer stick to Kaby Lake
如果你是一个纯粹的玩家，坚持选择Kaby Lake
if you are someone who's doing gaming and productivity like me doing photo editing and gaming
如果你是像我这样做游戏和生产性的像做照片编辑和游戏
then yeah you can look to what especially if you use a high resolution monitor like I do using a 4k display
那么是的，你可以看看特别是如果你使用高分辨率显示器，就像我使用4k显示器
seriously look at the 1800x because even though it doesn't do quite as good in gaming
认真看看1800x，因为即使在游戏方面也不尽如人意
are you really willing to pay all that extra money to get the 6900k?
你真的愿意支付所有额外的钱来获得6900k吗？
is it really going to be worth to you? I don't think so
这真的是值得吗？ 我不这么认为
and if you're just doing purely productivity stuff then one hundred percent look at this 1800x
如果你只是做纯粹的生产力，百分之百选择这个1800x
it could save your business quite a bit of money
它可以为您的业务节省相当多的钱
if you're just so on doing it harm it will also save you quite a bit of money
如果你怼它怼得十分凶猛，它也会节省你一点钱
and it would just do justice solid as the 6900k
它与6900k一样十分稳定
now i'll thank you for watching this video
感谢收看这个视频
please let me know what you guys think in the comments section down below
请让我知道你们的想法，在下面的评论区留言
I know this is going to be a crazy comments section i'm sure with everybody
我知道这将是一个疯狂的评论区，我相信你们
but try to keep so guys and try keep effectual and basis of what you've seen in this video
但是大家尽力保证评论的正确有效，有正确的观点理论你们在这个视频看到的
and other videos from other great tips* youtubers out there
和其他视频从其他厉害的youtubers
and as always I'll see you guys next time
和往常一样，我们下期再见。（大大的微笑）
学习交流之用，翻译水平有限，如果有问题请告知。
@95uxin个人站点：https://wuyu.xin
翻译：@深涧游鱼乐不知
校对、时间轴、部分听译：@95uxin